His, this is Liz Muller from Liz's Hair Design in Hollywood, Florida.
In this clip we're going to show you how to select hair care products.
We have all different types of hair care products, and this doesn't only have to do with shampoo and conditioner, OK. You might want to use a hydrating cream for your hair.
It's like a leave in, and the Moroccan Oil Company has a beautiful and brilliant hair styling cream that puts the shine, and it actually treats the hair while you roll or set it, or blow dry it, and it conditions that hair really nicely also.
You have also Singdellino that has Crystalli liquid, and this is fabulous, actually.
This liquid right here actually adds shine to the hair, leaving the hair soft, and it's wonderful.
You can actually put a little bit in the damp hair sometimes.
I do when I blow dry, but you can use it for every day, and it doesn't leave the hair oily.
You can actually use it on straight hair, they have a spray that's really light and that you can spray on the hair and it leaves a shine in the hair.
We have wonderful hair sprays.
This one's really light, I don't like anything too hard on the hair.
You can comb it out.
And if you have really fine hair and you want something to stay hard, then you might want to use a firm hold.
This is Liz Muller, and this is how you select hair care products.